# Ashish Tambe

DESKTOP SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

ashisht2629@outlook.com

9021112936

India, Maharashtra, Nagpur **Q** 

www.linkedin.com/in/ashish-tambe- in 214508316

#### **SUMMARY**

Who You Are: Bachelor s degree (IT related discipline preferred) 5.6 years IT experience including supporting end user technologies like desktop, Laptop, Mobile device, Microsoft office applications (Outlook, Teams, OneDrive, SharePoint, O365) Hand-on experience in IT technologies including basic networking, server hardware, Microsoft Active Directory, Telephony solutions, Cloud computing, DNS DHCP.

Proficient in troubleshooting hardware and software issues, configuring and maintaining desktop systems, and resolving connectivity problems.

#### **SKILLS**

- Troubleshooting
- Problemsolvina
- Hardware maintenance
- Software installation
- Network diagnostics
- Customer service
- Communication skills
- System upgrades
- Remote desktop
- MDM
- Active Directory, DHCP, DNS
- On-Boarding Off-Boarding
- Office-365
- Service now Service desk
- Desktop Central
- · Zoho Assists
- DL creation-Addition- modification
- Asset management
- OS installing
- US and Singapore user support
- Azure VM creation.
- Intune,MFA
- Microsoft Server Management
- Conference room support
- VIP Support
- Telephony solutions
- Cloud Computing

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Service desk Engineer

Divers Lynx May 2024 - Jun 2024

Working as Desktop Support and handling all kinds Troubleshooting, maintenance and service. As well as handling all kinds of computer hardware & maintenance. Installation, configuration & troubleshooting of Email and Network.

### **End User Support**

Infocepts (Chaitanya Solutions) Oct 2019 - May 2024

installing Operating Systems & troubleshooting of Daily Basis Problems, Preventive Maintenance

Having knowledge of Hardware, OS and Software Troubleshooting.

Installation & Troubleshooting of Windows 7, Windows 8, Windows 10

Installing application software as needed by user like MS-Office, Adobe reader etc

ID Creation and Dilation in Windows Server (AD) DNS DHCP

Outlook, MS Teams, Browser Issue

Remote Desktop Sharing Using MS Teams

Having Knowledge Service Desk Plus Ticketing tool.

Remote Support By Zoho Assist tool

Meeting room support using Kramer device for video conference

VIP Support

MDM (Intelligent hub & Intune) Configuration installation and troubleshooting

MFA Dual Authentication (DUO) and configuration and installation on mobile and laptop

Remote Desktop Support to Internal Associates regarding system issues, Application issues, O365 issues, Network issues, and VPN issues.

Providing support for Singapore and USA (Mclean office Internal user)

Office 365 DL Creation and password reset license assigned

Mac book support

Global protect VPN configuration installation & troubleshooting

Team lead support

Network printer management

### **Desktop Support**

Inknowtech PVT LTD Jan 2018 - Sep 2018

Working as a desktop support enginner handlling enf user supprort and on call support.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Diploma in Computer Engineering

Mahatma Gandhi Education Institute Of Management & Technology, Aug 2010 - Sep 2013

#### Hardware and Networking

Jetking Jun 2013 - Sep 2015

## **Bachelor of Computer Applications**

Malwanchal University Jul 2017 - Oct 2020

### **CERTIFICATION**

### Azure 104 Administration

Microsoft 2024-02-16

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Technical Support - Covid19

On Ground Technical Support - Covid19 Feb 2020 - Feb 2020

Enable all the IT realated work in just 3 days in th Covid situation.

also provided 400+ plus laptop to the assosiate to enable the organization work

# **LANGUAGES**

English

••••

Marathi



Hindi

